

Sara Abbasi UI/UX Designer

Date of birth: 1995

Address: Bussum, North Holland, Netherlands

Email: sara2196a@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/saraabasi

Portfolio: https://sarahbio.github.io/portfolio/

Hi! I'm Sara, a UI/UX designer and graduated with a BE of computer engineering(IT) based in Netherlands. I have been working for Paramount Students Company as a UI/UX designer for two years. I create modern and easy-to-use website and mobile designs. I mainly work in Figma. Feel free to message me, the quickest way to reach out to me is via an email. **I am looking for a new remote job.**

Resume

Employment

May 2023 - Present (+3 mos)
Product Designer at Paramount Students
Full time - Remote - London, England

December 2021 - May 2023 (1 yr 6 mos) UI/UX Designer at Paramount Students Full time - Remote - Istanbul, Turkey

Education

2014 – 2019 — Payam Noor UniversityBachelor of Computer Engineering (IT) - Iran

Specilizing

UI/UX

- Landing Page
- User Flow
- Wireframing
- Logo Design
- Prototyping
- Mockups
- Site Map

Technical Skills

Figma

Photoshop

Web Design (HTML/CSS)

Bootstrap

Languages

Persian

English

Turkish